Three AM the cursor blinks alone
새벽 세 시 커서는 혼자 깜빡이네.
A thousand functions no one's called
아무도 호출하지 않은 수많은 함수들.
The build keeps failing line by line
빌드는 줄줄이 계속 실패하고.
But I keep writing through the wall
하지만 난 벽을 뚫고 계속 써내려가.
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속에서 돌아가는 죽은 코드.
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스는 묻혀버린 불꽃.
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드하지 않고 아무도 플레이하지 않네.
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 아직도 켜져 있네.
Designed the maps drew every sprite
맵을 디자인했고 모든 스프라이트를 그렸지.
The folder grows the version climbs
폴더는 커지고 버전은 올라가네.
A finished game that no one finds
아무도 찾지 못하는 완성된 게임.
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속에서 돌아가는 죽은 코드.
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스는 묻혀버린 불꽃.
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드하지 않고 아무도 플레이하지 않네.
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 아직도 켜져 있네.